Hooded seals live in the Arctic.
Did you all know
that the hooded seal's lactation period is about four days?
They say that's the shortest of any mammal.
But setting that aside...
Japan is currently in the height of spring.
As a rain of pollen tickles my nasal membranes,
I, Andou Natsuki, have officially become a high school student.
Wrestling Club
Today is club recruiting day.
Let's ride horses!
High school is amazing!
There are so many different clubs!
H... H... Help me up...
I guess spring also brings along
some things I don't understand.
Stray seal!
What was that all about?
Hey, Nattsun!
Um... Who are you?
I'm Furuhashi! Furuhashi!
We went to middle school together!
This happens a lot!
Nattsun, your jokes are really too much.
I thought I told you to stop calling me
that once we were in high school.
Well? Have you picked your club yet, Nattsun?
Are you sticking with the Tennis Club?
Hmm... But doing the same thing as in middle school
wouldn't be very exciting.
Maybe I should be bold and try the Hundred Poems Club!
Huh?
Look! It's even the same arm motion.
As friends and strangers come and go...
I don't know if it's wise to join a club based on that.
Fault.
I don't like dealing with the hierarchies in clubs, anyway.
Maybe I should join the Going Home Club.
Really? Andou-san, you're joining the Going Home Club, too?
Um... you're Touno-san, right?
Yeah! I'm Touno Karin. It's nice to meet you!
But I'm so glad.
I thought I would be the only one joining the Going Home Club.
No, I really doubt that...
Furuhashi, you could join the Going Home Club—
What?! No, I've got my Hundred Poems Club!
Wasn't that just some idea you had?
Oh, right. I should go there and observe, or something.
That's right, that's right...
Observe?
Well, why don't we do the same?
Observe the Going Home Club! Yeah, right.
Sure, let's go!
Huh? What?
No, the Going Home Club isn't...
a...
real...
club...
Fire Prevention Supervisor:
Now Recruiting
Going Home Club
It is real!
Chronicles of the Going Home Club
Wait a minute.
Why does the Going Home Club have its own club room?!
That's taking "anything goes" too far!
It's amazing, isn't it?
Come in!
Have a little doubt here...
Record 1
Going Home Club Applicants
Excuse us!
Your membership is approved!
That was fast!
But you're applying for membership, right?
Yes!
I'm not really...
I'm so happy. What might your names be?
I'm Touno Karin!
I'm Andou Natsuki.
Karin-chan and Natsuki-chan, then!
Right! Let me introduce the crazy
members of the Going Home Club!
What?! The members are crazy?!
Sixteenth heir to the ancient
Hagizuki-ryuu martial arts style
Hagizuki-ryuu martial arts style,
Oohagi Botan-chan.
Let's fight bears together!
What?! She's exceptional!
Daughter of the head of the Kokonoe Corporation
Daughter of the head of the Kokonoe Corporation,
Kokonoe Claire-chan!
If we get any more members, we'll have to hire a maid.
What?! She's exceptional, too!
And I am the Going Home Club's president,
proud bearer of type A blood,
born under the sign of Taurus...
Doumyouji Sakura!
Name:  Doumyouji Sakura
Blood Type:                     A
Sign:                       Taurus
Height:                     163cm
Weight:                    Secret
Heir to my grandmother's sewing scissors!
Normal                                         Person
That means you're just an ordinary person!
L-Look.
I appreciate the introductions,
but I'm not actually interested in joining your club...
So can I go home now?
You...
You're incredible!
You want to go home right away...
You have incredible Going Home Spirit within you!
Huh?
That's right!
We must order dresses for the two of you right away!
Huh? W-Wait!
We've got some real Uber Loogies among us now.
If you're talking about an impressive newcomer,
the term is "Super Rookie"!
We've got two spirited first-years joining us!
This should be a lot of fun!
Welcome to the Going Home Club!
It's too soon for the ending theme!
Record 2
Life is Short; Go Home, Young Lady
So you ended up joining the Going Home Club yesterday!
This is no laughing matter.
But it's so funny, Nattsu—
Uh, I mean, um, Natsukichi?
You don't have to invent a new nickname for me, Furukawa.
It's Furuhashi.
Anyway, they told me to start coming officially, today.
What am I gonna do?
Well, it looks like not going isn't an option.
Hey, Andou-san.
You can call me Natsuki. And I'll call you Karin.
Really? Then can I call you Nat-chan?
Sure, fine with me.
So, what is it?
Nat-chan.
Nat-chan...
Blush
Um...
Oh, that's right.
Nat-chan, what do you think they
do in the Going Home Club?
You don't know?!
That's what I wanted to ask!
And what made you want to join
if you don't even know what they do?
What? Well, it was during club recruiting day...
Stand Up!
Going Home Club
Now Recruiting!
Stand! Stand up!
This is it!
What is it?!
What about that made you want to join their club?!
And they were recruiting people with that?!
I want to go home already.
That's a Super Rookie for you!
Shut up already.
It's okay, Nat-chan.
If you ask our senpai in Japanese,
I'm sure they'll tell you what the Going Home Club does.
Well, yes, that's probably true...
But it didn't occur to me that I had
a language choice besides Japanese.
Mohawk Seal!
Also known
as brush seal
Fire Prevention Supervisor: Seal
Going Home Club
Excuse me.
The first-years are here!
Welcome!
I've got controllers ready for you.
Oh, that's right. Chairs, chairs!
Um, Doumyouji-senpai...
Take no great pains. Prithee call me Sakura.
Okay, Sakura-senpai—
Aye, come nearer.
Sakura-senpai, why are you
using such old-timey language?
Probably because sixth period was classic literature.
She's so easily influenced!
Nat-chan. You wanted to ask something else, remember?
Oh, yeah.
Sakura-senpai.
What exactly does the Going Home Club do?
We have fun!
I told you, it's too soon!
How desperate are you to end the show?!
If you do nothing, your youth will pass by in an instant.
*Based on the creator's personal experience.
That is why we formed the Going Home Club,
to enjoy ourselves as much as possible
after school and on the way home.
Is that what it was?
Not even your own members knew?!
We want to do things that are fun, but that one shouldn't do.
Do things it's okay to do!
But today, we're going to do something it's okay to do.
Botan-chan! Claire-chan!
What are you going to do?
We're going to the park to feed the pigeons.
Feeding the pigeons!
Project Code...
MANNA!
It doesn't need a title that cool!
Feeding the pigeons? What are they, little kids?
There!
It's so fun!
Yeah! He took it!
Come on, little guy! It's tasty!
I guess... it might be kind of fun.
Chronicles of the Going Home Club
Going Home Club Photo Gallery
We took this photo of the
Going Home Club in action.
Who provides whose voice?
Chronicles of the Going Home Club
Just open it normally!
Record 3
Beware of Hagizuki-ryuu Practitioners
So, that was Botan-chan's demonstration
of Hagizuki-ryuu martial arts!
I'm impressed that you can cut it
so cleanly with just your bare hand.
To be precise, I'm not cutting it with my hand.
By moving my hand very quickly,
I create a momentary vacuum in the air.
That's what cuts it.
It's the same principle as the kamaitachi.
There it is! A manga explanation!
It's a closely guarded family secret, so don't tell anyone.
What?! You're taking a closely guarded secret pretty lightly!
But Botan-senpai really is strong, isn't she?
Yes. She's had many heroic exploits, as well.
Especially her "Bear Tour" last summer.
That was really scary!
What kind of ominous-sounding tour is that?
Botan-chan kept us up to date with very detailed emails...
July 28th
July 28th.
I'm fighting a brown bear in Hokkaido.
I knew it!
Why would you do something like that?!
I heard that the brown bear was the strongest
wild animal in Japan.
So I didn't have a choice.
Yes, you did!
And your reason doesn't have a shred
of high school girlishness in it!
The match was decided swiftly.
Was that all?
I was left with only disappointment.
You beat it?!
I beat the brown bear!
But I'm bummed by how weak it was.
Its punches looked like they weren't even moving.
Teehee.
It's a little late to bring out the
high school girl mannerisms in your emails!
And, send!
Don't get cocky... just because you beat me...
In Alaska, there dwells a bear far more powerful than I...
I felt as if the downed bear was speaking to me.
No! It absolutely was not speaking to you!
So, the brown bear was defeated.
But he was the weakest of us Four Bear Kings, so—
That didn't happen! I know it didn't!
July 30th, Alaska.
You flew to America?!
I found a grizzly in the forest.
Truly, he was a full size larger than the brown bear.
"I'm in America right now!
From: Oohagi Botan
Subject: America Now
I'm shocked by how big American hamburgers are!
I'm so stuffed!"
All you did was enjoy your first trip to America!
"And then I beat the bear."
The bear doesn't even matter anymore, does it?!
After defeating the grizzly, I realized...
Now that I'd come this far, I had to take on a polar bear.
Why?!
Bears get bigger and stronger the further north you go.
And I'd started feeling like I was playing a fighting game.
She's got game brain...
BOOM
July 31st.
I beat the polar bear, as well.
You did it?!
She beat the strongest bear
and we all assumed it was over.
But there was still more to come.
About a month later...
I read my cell phone bill and fell to pieces.
It's because you used your cell phone so much overseas!
It seems it wasn't bears I should have been fighting.
It was the system!
The system known as rate structure!
Rate structure
Just fix your rate plan and your lifestyle!
There were lots of others besides the bears.
She beat a great white shark in the ocean near Japan,
beat an elephant in Africa,
played with a squirrel at Tsurugaoka Hachiman Shrine,
beat a cobra in India...
I think a Kamakura vacation memory got
mixed up in there somewhere.
She also beat the Demon King with just the
You beat the Demon King!
Hero and no orbs of light!
And she beat the hardest final boss without taking any damage.
There's just no end to her heroic exploits.
Those last two were just challenge run stories!
That's how you end up with game brain!
The point that I want to instill
in you first-years as club president is that
Botan can only do these things because she received special training.
Ordinary people shouldn't try to mimic her!
Okay.
I've never heard a more unnecessary warning in my life.
That's right!
Now that we have new club members,
why don't you come fight bears with me for real?
We're going to that new crepe stand today.
Let it go.
Umm... I was sure it was in this area...
Oh, is that it there?
A bear!
Stop it.
Sorry for the wait!
Sakura-senpai, your crepe is so big!
Can you really finish all that?
Eh? Where's Natsuki-chan?
I believe she went to the powder room.
What's wrong? That was a strange noise.
The truth is...
School Store
at lunch, I went to the school store with Nat-chan...
But they were sold out of erasers.
The school store can sell out of erasers?
Yes...
Well, they actually did have some.
A whole display of them.
Nothing Comes Together As It Should
Huh?
But Karin didn't want one unless it was in a pink case.
I couldn't erase at all during my afternoon classes.
Just compromise and buy one!
That's tough.
Let's go buy you a stationery store later.
Buy a store?!
Record 4
Extravagant Youth: Priceless
Well, it can't be helped.
Claire-chan is the daughter of the Kokonoe Corporation, after all.
Her money sense is a little
different from a normal person's.
That's more than "a little" different!
Buying a store at the drop of a hat
is like "real-life sugoroku with actual
trains" level of money sense!
I just bought the whole store!
Claire-chan doesn't feel any sense of loss
when she spends money.
What are you talking about?
You know how when we turn on the faucet,
as much water comes out as we want?
Yeah...
That's how money is for her.
So she literally goes through money like water?
Her speech and behavior have always been extravagant.
She can summon a helicopter with the slightest gesture.
Or reserve an entire family restaurant.
My. Is that so?
Why did you get so many frames just now?!
What? I wasn't even thinking about it.
Try to avoid excessive movement!
This show is limited to *** frames!
This is what you call a true rich girl.
President, you saw right through it!
What? Everything's gone white...
I guess the effects are showing.
The seal is white, too.
These are the storyboards!
This is the linework!
But Claire's really living life on easy mode, huh?
You've always been able to get whatever you wanted, right?
Actually, it's more that by the
time I realize I want something,
I already have it.
She's on full auto mode! This is just like a crap game!
Hey, Natsuki-chan!
Be careful about making statements that could be construed
as calling movie-heavy games crap!
I didn't say anything like that!
Why are you being so oversensitive?!
Missile seal!
Setting that aside, you may be wondering why
such a rich girl would attend a school for normal people.
It's because Claire-chan has always longed for
a normal high school life.
I don't know if that's possible in a club like this.
It was my dream to walk home from school and attend
balls with my friends like a normal person.
In what dimension is that normal?
What? Was I wrong?
Well, that's the shape of it.
Natsuki-chan, Karin-chan.
You're both senpai when it comes to being commoners,
so show her the ropes.
Okay! Just leave it to me!
Claire-senpai, did you know about this?
The most delicious part of the ice cream
is not the ice cream itself,
but the part that gets stuck to the lid!
Oh, really?
That's not a "commoner" thought, it's a child's thought!
Ice cream...
comes with lids?
Okay! Today...
We will buy ice cream from the convenience store!
Convenience Store
Ice cream in a cup really is the best.
This is the way to go.
Buy ice cream in a cup!
Preview
Natsuki here!
I heard giant anteaters give birth standing up.
Spawning standing up?!
Next time, Record 5: The Cuckoo
Isn't Singing. It Appears to Be Dead.
And more!